<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>skills on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/skills/</link><description>Recent content in skills on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/skills/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Developing scenarios to help nurture Inclusive Research Leaders</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw22-inclusive-research-leaders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw22-inclusive-research-leaders/</guid><description>CW22 - 2022-04-04 Hack Day Idea: Albatross Hack Day Idea proposer Neil Chue Hong, Tracy Teal Hack Day Idea title (provisional) Developing scenarios to help nurture Inclusive Research Leaders
Hack day presentation Context and/or research domain Researchers and research software developers have developed experience and expertise in their areas of work. They have spent time learning how to code, analyze data and are experts in their domains. As people become leaders in their field, whether it’s a small group or a large team, they also need to develop leadership and management skills, but often haven’t had the opportunity to learn them, or are self-taught.</description></item><item><title>Hello world (of CI/CD)</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-hello-world-of-ci-cd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-hello-world-of-ci-cd/</guid><description>CW21 Hack Day - 2021-03-31 to 2021-04-01 Amonette-1943 - HP1-CW21
Hack Day idea Proposer Sorrel Harriet Idea name (provisional) Hello World! (of CI/CD)
Context / Research Domain Software engineering
Problem Build a Hello World app (but make it support continuous deployment.)
This hack day idea is more about developing skills, and less about the idea itself.
I want to gain experience using best practices like TDD and CI/CD, but I never seem to get around to actually doing it.</description></item><item><title>Koko</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-koko/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-koko/</guid><description>CW21 - 2021-03-30 Koko - CI11-CW21
Participants Stephan Druskat (stephan.druskat@dlr.de) Sammie Buzzard (BuzzardS@cardiff.ac.uk) Bailey Harrington (baileythegreen@gmail.com) Leyla Jael G. Castro (ljgarcia@zbmed.de) Abhishek Dasgupta (abhishek.dasgupta@cs.ox.ac.uk) The Adventurous Architect - \ A Blueprinter for Research Software Skills
Context / Research Domain Cross-domain (research software education/learning)
Problem Learners completing a basic Software (or other) Carpentry workshop don’t have clear next steps for how to continue their education, and those next steps will be different for many career paths.</description></item><item><title>Macavity</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-macavity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-macavity/</guid><description>CW21 - 2021-03-30 Macavity - CI13-CW21
Participants Louise Chisholm Malin Sandstrom (chair?) Florian Mannseicher Emma Karoune (scribe) Andrew Brown (scribe) IDEAS:
Skills Wheel for RSEs
Ideas:
Community management
How to be an RSE: define the professional identity, especially for young people starting out
_Training materials portal: practices, tools, languages etc. _
Carpentries address skills, this portal could address the (professional?) framework
Skills wheel
Different ways into RSE: direct training, researchers who incorporate RSE practices etc.</description></item></channel></rss>