<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tool on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/tool/</link><description>Recent content in tool on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/tool/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Credit All</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-credit-all/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-credit-all/</guid><description>CW21 Hack Day - 2021-03-31 to 2021-04-01 Booth-1948 - HP4-CW21
Hack Day idea proposer Emma Karoune (representing The Turing Way Community) Malin Sandstrom (INCF, CSCCE) Idea name (provisional) Inclusive authorship/contributor tool
Name ideas = Credit Me or All authors - Credit All Context and/or research domain Relevant to all domains to attribute contributions to research projects from all contributors more fairly in the authorship of academic publications.
Hack Day Demo Problem Current systems that attribute contributions to authors in academic outputs do not include all of the jobs/roles/tasks that are encompassed in research projects.</description></item><item><title>HowDescribedIs</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-howdescribedis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-howdescribedis/</guid><description>CW21 Hack Day - 2021-03-31 to 2021-04-01 Hopper-1949 - HP12-CW21
Hack Day idea proposer Faruk Diblen, Daniel Garijo, Carlos Martinez, Mathew Bluteau, Paddy McCann
Slack: #howdescribedis
Idea name (provisional) HowDescribedIs
Further automation of howfairis Hack Day Demo Context and/or research domain howfairis is a tool to measure level of adherence to the five recommendations on fair-software.eu website. It allows users to automatically check the compliance of their code and produce a badge displaying the score of their software.</description></item><item><title>SCAT (STEM Career Advising Tool)</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw18-scat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw18-scat/</guid><description>Collaborative Ideas for Group A - CI13-CW18
Reporter Mark Woodbridge - m.woodbridge@imperial.ac.uk
Participants Mark Woodbridge, Joanna Leng, Alexander Konovalov SCAT (STEM Career Advising Tool) Context / Research Domain There is a persistent and pervasive lack of diversity in STEM
Problem Highly capable individuals frequently make education and career choices in the absence of relevant or up-to-date information about the qualifications or skills required for specific roles.
Solution Building a course choice modeller which will permit to model how further career path may be influenced by course choices.</description></item></channel></rss>