<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>reproducibility on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/reproducibility/</link><description>Recent content in reproducibility on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/reproducibility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dealing with Legacy Code</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-legacy-code/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-legacy-code/</guid><description>CW20 - 2020-03-31 to 2020-04-02 Idea 4 - CI4-CW20
Dealing with Legacy Code
Participants Patricia Herterich_ _
Cat Smith_ _
Christopher Fullerton
Raniere Silva
Philipp Boersch-Supan
Context / Research Domain All research domains which have to contend with/rely on legacy code which does not conform to best practices.
Problem Researchers are instructed to use some legacy code written by their team, a third party or even themselves a while ago. The code isn&amp;rsquo;t documented or unit tested.</description></item><item><title>End of Life Plans for Software</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-assure-software-sustainability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-assure-software-sustainability/</guid><description>CW21 - 2021-03-30
Felix - CI6-CW21
Participants Eli Chadwick Iain Barrass Alice Minotto Yo Yehudi Context / Research Domain Planning for continuation of dissemination of research outputs is an established part of a research grant application. We frequently see requests for ongoing costs for website hosting, placement of datasets in repositories or hosting of developed code in an online version control system. However, it is less frequent that considerations are made of ongoing technical staff attention to support staff responsible for code sustainability, maintanence, or data updates.</description></item><item><title>Hello world (of CI/CD)</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-hello-world-of-ci-cd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-hello-world-of-ci-cd/</guid><description>CW21 Hack Day - 2021-03-31 to 2021-04-01 Amonette-1943 - HP1-CW21
Hack Day idea Proposer Sorrel Harriet Idea name (provisional) Hello World! (of CI/CD)
Context / Research Domain Software engineering
Problem Build a Hello World app (but make it support continuous deployment.)
This hack day idea is more about developing skills, and less about the idea itself.
I want to gain experience using best practices like TDD and CI/CD, but I never seem to get around to actually doing it.</description></item><item><title>HowDescribedIs</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-howdescribedis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-howdescribedis/</guid><description>CW21 Hack Day - 2021-03-31 to 2021-04-01 Hopper-1949 - HP12-CW21
Hack Day idea proposer Faruk Diblen, Daniel Garijo, Carlos Martinez, Mathew Bluteau, Paddy McCann
Slack: #howdescribedis
Idea name (provisional) HowDescribedIs
Further automation of howfairis Hack Day Demo Context and/or research domain howfairis is a tool to measure level of adherence to the five recommendations on fair-software.eu website. It allows users to automatically check the compliance of their code and produce a badge displaying the score of their software.</description></item></channel></rss>