<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rse on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/rse/</link><description>Recent content in rse on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/rse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DEPTH: Developer error/problem treasure hunt!</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-depth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-depth/</guid><description>CW21 - 2021-03-30 Garfield - CI7-CW21
Participants Matt Cannon - Taylor &amp;amp; Francis (scribe) Dominic Kempf / RSE, Heidelberg University Matthew Bluteau / RSE, UK Atomic Energy Authority Robin Wilson / Freelance - robin@rtwilson.com Paddy McCann / RSE, University of St Andrews Title: DEPTH: Developer Error/Problem Treasure Hunt! Context / Research Domain General RSE audiences, (and really any software developer)
Researchers who are not RSE - could have general or very specific queries.</description></item><item><title>Macavity</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-macavity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-macavity/</guid><description>CW21 - 2021-03-30 Macavity - CI13-CW21
Participants Louise Chisholm Malin Sandstrom (chair?) Florian Mannseicher Emma Karoune (scribe) Andrew Brown (scribe) IDEAS:
Skills Wheel for RSEs
Ideas:
Community management
How to be an RSE: define the professional identity, especially for young people starting out
_Training materials portal: practices, tools, languages etc. _
Carpentries address skills, this portal could address the (professional?) framework
Skills wheel
Different ways into RSE: direct training, researchers who incorporate RSE practices etc.</description></item><item><title>RSE2_D2</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-rse2_d2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-rse2_d2/</guid><description>CW20 - 2020-03-31 to 2020-04-02 RSE2_D2 - CI10-CW20
Participants Yo Yehudi - Software dev and EngD student (Cambridge and Manchester) David Perez-Suarez - RSE at UCL Blair Archibald - 2017 fellow, Postdoc Glasgow (soft spot for Haskell) Marion Weinzierl - RSE at Durham University, Not a fellow&amp;hellip; yet! Vahid Garousi - Belfast Context / Research Domain A long time ago, in an office far, far away, RSEs and researchers were developing software and may not be aware of all the good practices and are in need of a bit of motivation.</description></item></channel></rss>