<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>collaborations-workshop on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/collaborations-workshop/</link><description>Recent content in collaborations-workshop on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/collaborations-workshop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Conferencing 3.0: ensuring equality for in-person and online participants</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-conferencing3.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-conferencing3.0/</guid><description>CW20 - 2020-03-31 to 2020-04-02 “Conferencing 3.0: ensuring equality for in-person and online participants” - CI2-CW20
Participants Emily Lewis Esther Asef Radovan Bast Bezaye Tesfaye Neil Chue Hong Richard Darst Context / Research Domain When the COVID-19 lockdown restrictions lift, we will see a return to people wanting to restart in-person events whilst others will want to continue the online interactions. The challenge will be to create a combination of guidance and tools to help run events when we have mixed online and in-person interaction, to make sure we don’t introduce new issues?</description></item><item><title>Exploratory analysis of past Collaborative Ideas</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-exploratory-analysis-of-past-collaborative-ideas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-exploratory-analysis-of-past-collaborative-ideas/</guid><description>CW21 Hack Day - 2021-03-31 to 2021-04-01 Fox-1940 - HP9-CW21
Hack Day idea proposer Heather Turner Idea name (provisional) Exploratory analysis of past Collaborative Ideas
Hack Day Demo Problem Many of Collaborative Ideas have been proposed at past Collaborations Workshops. It would be great if there was a way to explore these ideas to see if there are recurrent themes, if proposed ideas have been taken on, etc. It would be useful for workshop organizers to identify potential themes/ideas for future events, e.</description></item></channel></rss>