<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>open-source on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/open-source/</link><description>Recent content in open-source on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/open-source/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Easy Open Source Bio-Graphs</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw22-easy-open-source-biographs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw22-easy-open-source-biographs/</guid><description>CW22 - 2022-04-04 Collaborative Ideas session group: A-Aloe Biological Sciences.
Participants Mark Basham, Rosalind Franklin Institute, mark.basham@rfi.ac.uk - note taker
Gemma Turon, Ersilia Open Source Initiative, gemma@ersilia.io
Sarah Forrester, University of York, sarah.forrester@york.ac.uk - chair
Emma Karoune, The Alan Turing Institute, ekaroune@turing.ac.uk
Vicky Hellon, The Alan Turing Institute, vhellon@turing.ac.uk
Katy Brown, University of Cambridge, kab84@cam.ac.uk
Collaborative Idea Title Easy Open Source Bio-Graphs
Context / Research Domain Many biological labs have routine assays or experiments which require standard analysis and produce a well understood graph as an output.</description></item><item><title>Open Source Covid Analysis of References (OSCAR)</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-oscar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-oscar/</guid><description>CW21 - 2021-03-30 Oscar - CI15-CW21
Participants Michelle Barker Shoaib Suf Daniel S Katz Carina Haupt Callum Rollo Title: Open Source Covid Analysis of References (OSCAR) Context / Research Domain Software’s use in the Covid19 pandemic is somewhat hidden but ubiquitous. Understanding the impact of software in the pandemic would give it the credit that software deserves, raise its profile and potentially highlight the software readiness that would help in any future public health emergency.</description></item></channel></rss>