<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>project on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/project/</link><description>Recent content in project on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to manage expectations while juggling different projects with overlapping deadlines and competing resources?</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw18-managing-expectations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw18-managing-expectations/</guid><description>Collaborations Workshop 2018 - 2018-03-26 How to manage expectations while juggling different projects with overlapping deadlines and competing resources? - CI1-CW18
Reporter Tania R Allard - t.allard@sheffield.ac.uk
Participants Stephan Druskat, Robert Haines, Tania Allard, Mark Woodbridge, Stuart Grieve, Brigitta Sipocz, Alejandra Gonzalez-Beltran, Raquel Alegre
Context / Research Domain This problem is often found within Research Software Engineering like-teams working collaboratively in a number of research projects.
Problem Now that the necessity of having an RSE in a project is established, the issue of managing the expectations of the projects and allocating resources to multiple concurrent projects.</description></item><item><title>Leo</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-leo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-leo/</guid><description>CW21 - 2021-03-30 Leo - CI12-CW21
Participants Emma Rand emma.rand@york.ac.uk Aida Mehonic Hannah Williams Hannah.Williams@phe.gov.uk Carlos Martinez-Ortiz _Flic Anderson contact@felicityanderson.co.uk _ ConnECT ProjECT - an Exciting Collaboration Tool for discovering project similarities Context / Research Domain Collaboration - not research domain specific
Problem _Lots of individuals/groups working on projects (for example a large funded project), but it can be difficult to identify commonalities, opportunities for collaboration and start useful discussions. _</description></item></channel></rss>