<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>funding on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/funding/</link><description>Recent content in funding on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/funding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to encourage and ensure software maintenance gets sufficiently funded</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-getting-software-maintenance-funded/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-getting-software-maintenance-funded/</guid><description>CW21 - 2021-03-30 Bagpuss - CI2-CW21
Participants Sorrel Harriet (Chair) Teri Forey (Scribe) Diego Alonso Álvarez Heather Turner Alexander Konovalov Ilian Todorov Ideas:
_Tool or mechanism to add comments to code, or annotating the code with feedback without creating a pull request. Better space to provide guidance. _ _Nothing wrong with paired programming or code review, but it’s synchronous (have to find time that’s convenient to everyone). If it’s in a document there’s no easy way to link it to the line of code.</description></item><item><title>Tools to recognise underlying software infrastructure visible and funded</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-tools-to-recognise-underlying-software-infrastructure-visible-and-funded/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-tools-to-recognise-underlying-software-infrastructure-visible-and-funded/</guid><description>CW21 Hack Day - 2021-03-31 to 2021-04-01 Hermann-1926 - HP11-CW21
Hack Day idea proposer Louise Chisholm Idea name (provisional) Tools to recognise underlying software infrastructure visible &amp;amp; funded
Context and/or research domain Research often relies on underlying software infrastructure, but their contribution is not recognised and it is difficult to attract funding to maintain software infrastructure.
Problem Research often relies on underlying software infrastructure, but their contribution is not recognised and it is difficult to attract funding to maintain software infrastructure.</description></item></channel></rss>