<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>collaboration on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/collaboration/</link><description>Recent content in collaboration on Collaborations Workshop Ideas &amp; Pitches</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/tags/collaboration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AutoSoftCat</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw18-autosoftcat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw18-autosoftcat/</guid><description>Collaborations Workshop 2018 - 2018-03-26 Group K - CI2-CW18
AutoSoftCat Reporter Dave McKain - davemckain@gmail.com
Participants Alys Brett - alys.brett@ukaea.uk
Alexander.Struck@hu-berlin.de
Caroline Jay caroline.jay@manchester.ac.uk
Context / Research Domain Discoverability of software for potential reuse or collaboration is an issue that is common across research domains.
Problem Software is hard to find. If published at all, software is located in many places, which varies according to the underlying discipline or domain.</description></item><item><title>Equitable Collaboration guide for distributed/online teams and communities in The Turing Way</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-collaboration-turing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-collaboration-turing/</guid><description>2CW20 - 2020-03-31 to 2020-04-02 Epsilon - Equitable Collaboration guide for distributed/online teams and communities in The Turing Way - HP5-CW20
**Hackday Idea Proposer: The Turing Way Community Members ** **Overview: **
There are three pitches (idea 2, idea 5 and idea 8) that can be used as a combined solution to this pitch (see below).
Context / Research Domain
Remote collaboration has gained popularity over the last years as more and more companies expand their business in areas far from the location of the main office (for example, Mozilla), or exist entirely as a remote company (for example, RStudio).</description></item><item><title>How do we facilitate effective collaboration in a virtual event?</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-facilitating-virtual-event-collab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-facilitating-virtual-event-collab/</guid><description>CW20 - 2020-03-31 to 2020-04-02 Beta - HP2-CW20
Hackday Idea Proposer Emmy (slack @Emmy Tsang)
Context / Research Domain Many collaborative events / workshops are moving online because of the COVID-19 situation; but more generally– can we run events like the CW hackday online, and what would it take?
Problem How do we facilitate effective collaboration in a virtual event, where:
People have to work across multiple time zones: all conversations/communications need to be documented some way on a channel that everyone in the team (at least) can access and consume easily It’s more difficult, esp for newcomers, to get to know other people There’s a lack of watercooler/coffee machine conversations Version control and tracking changes could be trickier?</description></item><item><title>Leo</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-leo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw21-leo/</guid><description>CW21 - 2021-03-30 Leo - CI12-CW21
Participants Emma Rand emma.rand@york.ac.uk Aida Mehonic Hannah Williams Hannah.Williams@phe.gov.uk Carlos Martinez-Ortiz _Flic Anderson contact@felicityanderson.co.uk _ ConnECT ProjECT - an Exciting Collaboration Tool for discovering project similarities Context / Research Domain Collaboration - not research domain specific
Problem _Lots of individuals/groups working on projects (for example a large funded project), but it can be difficult to identify commonalities, opportunities for collaboration and start useful discussions. _</description></item><item><title>Message in e-Bottle: work more effectively with ephemeral teams across timezones</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-message-in-ebottle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-message-in-ebottle/</guid><description>CW20 - 2020-03-31 to 2020-04-02 Idea 3 - Message in e Bottle: work more effectively with ephemeral teams across timezones. - CI3-CW20
Participants Shoaib Sufi (shoaib.sufi@software.ac.uk), Carlos Martinez (c.martinez@esciencecenter.nl) (scribe), Alessandro Felder (a.felder@ucl.ac.uk) (chair), Emmy Tsang (e.tsang@elifesciences.org), Aleksandra Nenadic (a.nenadic@manchester.ac.uk) Original slide at - _https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1GbwxVrWpqw_Nk9Mg9dinLUUThHSfetVsg7KD2SiGIkk/edit?usp=sharing _
Context / Research Domain Are you:
A workshop host delivering a session to participants from multiple time zones? A hackathon organiser facilitating collaborations between newcomers and experienced community members in teams spread across different time zones?</description></item><item><title>The Turing Way</title><link>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-the-turing-way/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://softwaresaved.github.io/CW-ideas/cw20-the-turing-way/</guid><description>CW20 - 2020-03-31 to 2020-04-02 Remote Conferences and Collaboration: The Turing Way - CI5-CW20
Participants Sarah Gibson, Stephan Druskat, Louise Brown, Jurriaan H.Spaaks, Sam Mangham
Context / Research Domain Issues on The Turing Way repository
Due to the current COVID-19 crisis, remote work has become the default mode of working for most people in research, but it has also been common practice for different people and projects before that. How can we, working remotely, maintain the communities in this mode, and make sure that the community and the people involved in it remain healthy, and productive, and have all the information and technical support they need?</description></item></channel></rss>